{
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "Which sentence is grammatically correct: 'She don't like pizza.' or 'She doesn't like pizza.'?",
        "options": ["She don't like pizza.", "She doesn't like pizza."],
        "correctOption": "She doesn't like pizza."
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "What is the plural form of 'mouse'?",
        "options": ["Mouses", "Mice", "Moo"],
        "correctOption": "Mice"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "Choose the correct verb form: 'He ________ to the store yesterday.'",
        "options": ["Go", "Goes", "Went"],
        "correctOption": "Went"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "Identify the adverb in the sentence: 'She sings beautifully.'",
        "options": ["She", "Sings", "Beautifully"],
        "correctOption": "Beautifully"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "What is the comparative form of 'good'?",
        "options": ["Gooder", "Better", "More good"],
        "correctOption": "Better"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "Choose the correct form: 'I prefer coffee than tea.' or 'I prefer coffee to tea.'",
        "options": ["I prefer coffee than tea.", "I prefer coffee to tea."],
        "correctOption": "I prefer coffee to tea."
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "Which word is a conjunction in the sentence: 'He will come if you invite him.'?",
        "options": ["He", "Will", "If"],
        "correctOption": "If"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "What is the past participle of 'eat'?",
        "options": ["Eaten", "Ate", "Eating"],
        "correctOption": "Eaten"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "In the sentence 'The cat sat on the mat,' what is the preposition?",
        "options": ["Cat", "Sat", "On"],
        "correctOption": "On"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "language": "english",
        "question": "Which sentence is in the passive voice: 'The teacher praised the students.' or 'The students were praised by the teacher.'?",
        "options": ["The teacher praised the students.", "The students were praised by the teacher."],
        "correctOption": "The students were praised by the teacher."
      }

    ]
  }